[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110504pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ":", "NNP", ",", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "NN", ",", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "WP", "VBD", "VBN", ":", "VBD", "VBN", "NNS", "TO", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 55, "question": "Can you describe them to me?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 56, "answer": "OGERS: Well, as a former law enforcement agent, much like the crime scene photo where you would see a victim who had been -- had suffered gunshots to the head.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110504pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 61, "question": "I mean are they, would you say, similar to the images we've seen of the other victims of the raid?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBP", "PRP", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", ",", "JJ", "TO", "DT", "NNS", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 62, "answer": "I think so.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110504pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 64, "question": "I mean, would you argue personally that they are just from a taste point of view too graphic, too gruesome, to be published?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "RB", "JJ", ",", "RB", "RB", ",", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 65, "answer": "Yes, I think they're fairly tough to look at.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110504pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "POS", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 119, "question": "Look, what's your take on all this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 120, "answer": "Well, first of all, on the operation, it was a great tribute to the president's courage that he ordered this operation.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110504pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 136, "question": "The issue I think is more a question of, would it affect national security and would it put our troop's lives at risk if you inflame the Muslim community by publishing them?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBZ", "RBR", "DT", "NN", "IN", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "MD", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "POS", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 137, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110504pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 161, "question": "So the morality of all this is a little bit skewed, to put it mildly, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "DT", "VBZ", "DT", "RB", "NN", "VBD", ",", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "RB", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 162, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110504pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["JJS", "NNS", "RB", "VBP", "RB", "CC", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "CC", "WP", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 195, "question": "I mean, what kind of reputation did he have by the end amongst the Pakistani community?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "WP", "NN", "IN", "NN", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 196, "answer": "Most people here are sick and tired of him and what he's brought to the country.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110504pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "DT", "NNS", "RB", ",", "RB", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "JJ", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 233, "question": "Why on this occasion would you prefer it not to be?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "RB", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 234, "answer": "Well, of course, I'm tempted to say that you know if somebody wants to leak me the photos exclusively, then hey, you know, give me a call at the office.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110504pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "NN", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 237, "question": "I mean, would \"The New York Times\" have published these pictures if they'd been offered to them?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "MD", "``", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "''", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 238, "answer": "Well, look, I mean, we're in -- we're in the business of getting information out.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110504pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 243, "question": "What is your reaction to the news that they won't be published?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 244, "answer": "I think it's a terrible mistake.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["First Amendment"]}, "docId": "110504pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "IN", "POS", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 268, "question": "What do we really gain by seeing an image of that given we know that's what happened?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "VBN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "POS", "WP", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 269, "answer": "Under the First Amendment, that's the wrong question.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110504pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 284, "question": "Do you agree with him?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 285, "answer": "I do.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110504pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "VB", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 315, "question": "What do you say to that, Nick Kristof?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "DT", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 316, "answer": "Well, I mean, I don't really buy that.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Nick Kristof"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110504pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "DT", "NN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 326, "question": "In your legal opinion, was it lawful?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBD", "PRP", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 327, "answer": "If it went down that the way the administration says it went down, it was lawful.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110504pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "CD", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 351, "question": "That, in terms of morality, seems a pretty flawed double position, doesn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "DT", "RB", "VBN", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 352, "answer": "Well, it's one of many positions where we're just completely hypocritical.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110504pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "EX", "RB", "VBP", "VBN", "NNS", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "VBN", "NNP", "WP", "POS", "VBN", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 362, "question": "Isn't it the easier thing to just say, you know what, here he is, move on?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "DT", "JJR", "NN", "TO", "RB", "VB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "WP", ",", "RB", "PRP", "VBZ", ",", "NN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 363, "answer": "Yes, there certainly have been doubts about whether it really was bin Laden who's been killed.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110504pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 374, "question": "Aren't they entitled to an image to atone for all the terrible images he inflicted on the American people?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "DT", "NN", "TO", "NN", "IN", "DT", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 375, "answer": "We apply a double standard on outrage.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110504pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 389, "question": "Let me ask Alan Dershowitz one difficult question, which is this, which is, if the military, as we understand, made a plea for these photographs not to be released, because they genuinely feared there would be reprisals against servicemen in Afghanistan and Iraq, is that not a compelling reason alone not to publish them?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "NNP", "NNP", "CD", "NN", "NN", ",", "WDT", "VBZ", "DT", ",", "WDT", "VBZ", ",", "IN", "DT", "JJ", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "RB", "TO", "VB", "VBN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "EX", "MD", "VB", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", ",", "VBZ", "IN", "RB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "NN", "RB", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 390, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Iraq"], "LOCATION": ["Afghanistan"], "PERSON": ["Alan Dershowitz"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Khalid Sheikh Mohammed"], "LOCATION": ["Guantanamo"]}, "docId": "110504pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "WP", "VBN", "CC", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "IN", "NNP", ",", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "CD", "JJ", "NN", "NNP", "WP$", "RB", "RB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 471, "question": "What were your feelings when you first heard bin Laden was dead?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NNS", "WRB", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "NN", "NNP", "VBD", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 472, "answer": "I felt happy that the man who bragged and said that he killed my son, like Khalid Sheikh Mohammed did at Guantanamo, bragging that they killed my son and 3,000 other innocent American whose only crime was they went to work -- I felt good about it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110504pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "RB", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 484, "question": "Would it give you any kind of solace?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 485, "answer": "No, not at all.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110504pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "NNP", "RB", "VBD", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", ",", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 507, "question": "Without a picture, are you entirely satisfied that it was bin Laden, that he is dead?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 508, "answer": "Well, as Jim just said, I'm going to believe the president, take him at his word.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["Sunday"], "TIME": ["night"]}, "docId": "110504pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", "WDT", "IN", "IN", "CD", "IN", "NNP", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "RB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "CC", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 518, "question": "How will you be feeling tomorrow when this very emotional visit takes place?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBG", "NN", "WRB", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 519, "answer": "I think I can speak for so many families that since about 11:00 on Sunday night, it's been quite a wild ride of emotions and exhaustion.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Obama"]}, "docId": "110504pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NNS", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "CC", "VB", "NN", "NNP", "CC", "VB", "PRP", "RP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "PRP", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 532, "question": "What will your feelings be?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "VB", "NNS", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 533, "answer": "My feelings are I want to extend my internal gratitude to President Obama for having the backbone to make the attack and get bin Laden and take him out, like he promised to us before.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110504pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "RB", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 595, "question": "Brandon, when you hear the president talk about the morality of not releasing this picture, of doing the right thing, it's not what America does, what is your take, given you were at Guantanamo watching and witnessing some pretty outrageous stuff being carried out in America's name?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "RB", "VBG", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "WP", "NNP", "VBZ", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "VBN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NNP", "NN", "CC", "VBG", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "VBG", "VBN", "RP", "IN", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 596, "answer": "I can understand him not releasing the photo.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America", "Guantanamo", "America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110504pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 598, "question": "But in relation to what you witnessed -- I mean, you saw, I would argue from what I read of your testimony before, flagrant abuses of the Geneva Convention and of justice, didn't you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "NN", "TO", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", ",", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "IN", "NN", ",", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 599, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Geneva Convention"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110504pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 605, "question": "For everything that you saw, do you think that torture in any guise, whether it's semi-permissible, like waterboarding -- does it ever work, from what you saw?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", ",", "IN", "NN", ":", "VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "VB", ",", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 606, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]